,entities,headline,url,website
0,[],What you need to know,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
1,"[('tonight', 'TIME'), ('Pelosi', 'ORG')]","No deal reached tonight on coronavirus response package, Pelosi says",https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
2,"[('Billie Eilish', 'PERSON')]",Singer Billie Eilish postpones tour dates over coronavirus outbreak,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
3,"[('CNN', 'ORG')]",SOON: CNN's coronavirus town hall,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
4,"[('Disney World', 'ORG'), ('Disneyland Paris Resort', 'ORG')]","Disney World, Disneyland Paris Resort to close over coronavirus concerns",https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
5,"[('Pennsylvania Department of Corrections', 'ORG'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE')]",Pennsylvania Department of Corrections suspending most prison visits starting tomorrow,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
6,"[('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3 weeks', 'DATE')]",New Mexico to close all K-12 public schools for 3 weeks,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
7,"[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Cleveland Cavaliers', 'ORG')]",NBA's Cleveland Cavaliers to compensate all stadium employees regular wages,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
8,"[('Kansas', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]",Kansas announces first coronavirus death,https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/coronavirus-outbreak-03-12-20-intl-hnk/index.html,CNN
9,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('100,000-240,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), (""two weeks'"", 'DATE')]","Americans told to prepare for 100,000-240,000 coronavirus deaths as Trump predicts 'very painful two weeks'",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
10,"[('NBC News', 'ORG'), ('Savannah Guthrie', 'PERSON'), ('Hoda Kotb', 'PERSON')]","Watch live / 'Coronavirus Pandemic,' an NBC News special report hosted by Savannah Guthrie and Hoda Kotb",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
11,[],Live Blog / Latest news on the global pandemic,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
12,[],Trump sees ghosts of hometown past and election future in COVID-19,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
13,"[('Texas', 'GPE')]",Texas 'mom and pop' business flooded with orders for helmet ventilators,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
14,"[('Congress', 'ORG')]",Jockeying begins in Congress over the next coronavirus relief bill,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
15,"[('Congressional Hispanic Caucus', 'ORG')]",Congressional Hispanic Caucus calls on ICE to release detainees amid COVID-19 crisis,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
16,"[(""Larry David's"", 'PERSON')]","Larry David's coronavirus PSA: Stay home, watch TV and stop 'hurting old people like me'",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
17,"[('Asian', 'NORP'), ('Hispanic', 'NORP'), ('House', 'ORG')]","Black, Asian and Hispanic House caucus chairs unite in 'no tolerance' for coronavirus racism",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
18,"[('César Chávez Day', 'ORG')]","On César Chávez Day, Biden calls for coronavirus protections for farmworkers",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
19,[],Rent's due. Now what? Experts warn a housing crisis shadows the health crisis.,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
20,[],"Fearing COVID-19 spread to families, health care workers self-isolate at home",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
21,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]",Wall Street just had one of its worst quarters in history,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
22,"[('New York', 'GPE')]",New York man exposed to coronavirus hid symptoms to visit wife in hospital,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
23,"[('Chicago', 'GPE')]",'Where's Lightfoot' memes show Chicago mayor guarding city,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
24,"[('28', 'CARDINAL'), ('University of Texas', 'ORG')]",28 University of Texas spring breakers test positive for COVID-19,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
25,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG')]",Coronavirus deniers take aim at hospitals as pandemic grows,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
26,"[('Union', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('UPS', 'ORG'), ('Massachusetts', 'GPE')]",Union says 3 UPS employees test positive for COVID-19 at same Massachusetts facility,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
27,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]","Consumer confidence nosedives, as U.S. braces for economic pain",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
28,"[('Louisiana', 'GPE')]",Louisiana pastor charged with defying coronavirus order against large gatherings,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
29,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]",U.S. faces unparalleled challenge evacuating diplomats amid coronavirus,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
30,"[('McConnell', 'PERSON'), ('Impeachment', 'PERSON')]",McConnell: Impeachment 'diverted' attention from coronavirus concerns,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
31,[],'I hate COVID-19': Kids with disabilities struggle to adjust as schools close,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
32,[],Cooking more at home? Roasting vegetables makes healthy eating easier,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
33,"[('COVID-19 era', 'DATE')]",Essence virtual summit set to help black women cope in COVID-19 era,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
34,[],They were expecting a baby via surrogate. Then the COVID-19 pandemic put it all on hold,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
35,"[('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('last day', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP')]",Harry and Meghan bid farewell on last day as British royals,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
36,[],Doctor who got pulled over speeding got face masks instead of a ticket,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
37,"[('Pelosi', 'CARDINAL'), ('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]","Pelosi: 'I kept my distance' from members at Capitol, including one presumed to have coronavirus",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
38,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]",Africa's mountain gorillas also at risk from coronavirus,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
39,"[('Americans', 'NORP')]",The stimulus check won't be in the mail for Americans who owe child support,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
40,"[('New Jersey', 'GPE')]",New Jersey parents charged with child endangerment for hosting party,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
41,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('NYC', 'ORG')]",Amazon fires warehouse worker who led NYC strike for more coronavirus protection,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
42,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]","U.S. coronavirus death toll passes 3,000 as Spain and Italy honor their dead",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
43,[],Most cruise lines don't pay federal income tax — just one of the reasons they aren't getting a bailout,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
44,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Massachusetts', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]",11 vets die at Massachusetts facility; 5 tested positive for COVID-19,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
45,"[('Vegas', 'GPE')]",Vegas invited homeless to parking lot after virus closed shelter,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
46,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP')]","Facebook, Twitter bar video of Brazilian president endorsing unproven antiviral drug",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
47,"[('Rose Garden', 'LOC')]",Trump fluffs MyPillow in Rose Garden coronavirus talk,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
48,[],Congressional leaders confident in oversight of economic package despite signing statement,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
49,"[('Florida', 'GPE')]",A coronavirus-stricken cruise ship is approaching Florida. Will it be allowed to dock?,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
50,"[('400', 'CARDINAL')]",Number of long-term care facilities with COVID-19 cases tops 400 nationwide,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
51,"[('Florida', 'GPE')]",Florida pastor arrested after holding church services despite coronavirus orders,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
52,"[('New York City', 'GPE')]",'I fear for my life': Prisoners in New York City jails sound alarm as coronavirus spreads,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
53,"[('Central Park', 'LOC')]","'It's surreal,' nurse practitioner says of Central Park field hospital",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
54,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG')]",Coronavirus medication shortages could be invisible until it is virtually too late,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
55,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('Detroit', 'GPE'), ('Michigan', 'GPE')]",Coronavirus comes for Detroit: Why certain Michigan residents are at higher risk,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
56,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG')]",Coronavirus strains rural hospitals 'to the absolute limit',https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
57,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]",No evidence for Trump's saying masks 'going out the back door' of NY hospitals,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
58,[],Man planned to bomb hospital during pandemic to publicize white supremacist views,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
59,"[('Kentucky', 'GPE')]",'This virus is no joke': Kentucky officials don't wait for surge of coronavirus cases to tighten restrictions,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
60,[],"Some Instacart workers strike, others demand more as coronavirus alters labor landscape",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
61,"[('Velazquez', 'PERSON'), ('Pelosi', 'ORG'), ('last week', 'DATE')]","Rep. Velazquez has presumed COVID-19 infection, was near Pelosi, other lawmakers last week",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
62,[],"Affairs, hoarders and hope: Read anonymous confessions in the time of the coronavirus",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
63,[],Coronavirus: What you need to know,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
64,[],Photos capture empty cities across the globe,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
65,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Guaidó', 'GPE')]",Venezuela's Guaidó calls for coalition government to fight the coronavirus,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
66,"[('New York City', 'GPE')]",First minor with coronavirus in New York City dies,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
67,"[('7', 'CARDINAL')]",7 ways to set boundaries when working from home,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
68,"[('Formula 1', 'PERSON')]",Formula 1 official suggested drivers infect themselves with coronavirus,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
69,"[('Macy', 'ORG')]","Macy's to furlough most of 130,000-strong workforce",https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
70,[],Cooped up at home? You can help scientists spot penguins from space or seek out new galaxies,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
71,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('below $1 per gallon', 'MONEY')]",U.S. set to lose title as top oil producer as demand plunges and gas drops below $1 per gallon,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
72,"[('Coronavirus', 'ORG'), ('FBI', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]",Coronavirus kickbacks: FBI arrests Georgia man accused of unnecessary testing scam,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
73,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]",Trump administration in talks with India to avoid U.S. drug supply shortage,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
74,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]",U.S. vets volunteer to patrol SF Chinatown,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
75,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maryland', 'GPE'), ('66', 'CARDINAL')]",Nursing homes hit hard by coronavirus; one Maryland home reports 66 cases,https://www.nbcnews.com/health/coronavirus,NBC
76,[],Latest news for health care. ,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
77,"[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('50.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('March', 'DATE')]",Results of a private survey released on Wednesday showed China's manufacturing activity 50.1 in March as factories began to come online amid a coronavirus outbreak.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
78,"[('HSBC', 'ORG'), ('9.5%', 'PERCENT'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Standard Chartered', 'ORG'), ('7.18%', 'PERCENT'), ('9:36 a.m.', 'TIME')]",HSBC shares fell 9.5% in Hong Kong and Standard Chartered was down 7.18% as of 9:36 a.m. HK/SIN.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
79,"[('Maine', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')]",Maine became the latest state Tuesday to order residents to remain at home during the coronavirus pandemic.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
80,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]","President Donald Trump prepared Americans for a surge in coronavirus cases, saying the U.S. is facing a ""very, very painful two weeks.""",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
81,"[('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('Carnival', 'ORG'), ('Zaandam', 'PERSON'), ('15 days', 'DATE')]","Of the nine ships, the one getting the most attention is the Carnival-owned MS Zaandam which has been at sea for 15 days.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
82,"[('app to 90 days', 'DATE')]","The digital fitness company extended the free trial of its app to 90 days, which led to a surge in downloads as gyms across the nation close due to stay-at-home mandates",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
83,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ian Lipkin', 'PERSON'), ('CNBC', 'ORG')]","""One of the things we need to learn from this is we have to invest in our public health infrastructure, invest in our science ... so things like this never happen again,"" Dr. Ian Lipkin told CNBC.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
84,"[('Four days', 'DATE'), ('an unprecedented $2 trillion', 'MONEY'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('$2 trillion', 'MONEY')]","Four days after signing an unprecedented $2 trillion relief bill to blunt the economic damage from the coronavirus pandemic, the president on Tuesday called for the U.S. to spend another $2 trillion on a massive infrastructure package.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
85,"[('California', 'GPE'), ('Gavin Newsom', 'PERSON'), ('May 2020', 'DATE'), ('Health Corps', 'ORG'), ('25,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('its first day', 'DATE')]","According to models used by the state, California Governor Gavin Newsom said he expects the COVID-19 outbreak to peak there some time in May 2020. To fight the pandemic, the state has asked licensed health professionals to raise their hands to work via a new Health Corps site, which scored 25,000 sign-ups in its first day.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
86,"[('USTA', 'ORG'), ('Queens', 'GPE'), ('350', 'CARDINAL'), ('Elmhurst Hospital', 'ORG')]",Part of the USTA Billie Jean King National Tennis Center in Queens will be converted into a temporary hospital with 350 beds for non-ICU patients from Elmhurst Hospital.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
87,"[('New York', 'GPE')]","Domestic violence programs and shelters in New York, the state with the most coronavirus cases, are seeing a decline in at-risk clients, who are staying home as the disease spreads.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
88,"[('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Bill de Blasio', 'PERSON'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('more than 43,100', 'CARDINAL')]","New York City Mayor Bill de Blasio is holding a press conference Monday to update the public on the coronavirus outbreak that has infected more than 43,100 people in the city.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
89,"[('New Jersey', 'GPE'), ('Phil Murphy', 'PERSON'), ('more than 16,636', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')]","New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy is holding a press conference on the COVID-19 outbreak, which has infected more than 16,636 people in the state as of Tuesday.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
90,"[('JetBlue', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE')]",JetBlue is the latest carrier to slash flights in the New York area because of coronavirus warnings.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
91,"[('Ed Boyle', 'PERSON'), ('Bend', 'GPE'), ('Oregon', 'GPE'), ('Ida Azul', 'PERSON')]","Dr. Ed Boyle is trying to keep a brave face for his staff in Bend, Oregon, but revenue has taken a huge hit now that his medical practice can no longer perform elective procedures during the coronavirus shutdown. His wife, Dr. Ida Azul, is in the same boat.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
92,"[('Dan Schulman', 'PERSON'), ('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')]","""We don't intend to do any layoffs as a result of COVID-19,"" PayPal CEO Dan Schulman told CNBC on Tuesday.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
93,"[('day one', 'DATE'), ('Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')]","""We have been behind it from day one since it got here. We have been playing catch up,"" Cuomo said Tuesday in announcing the new cases.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
94,"[('Chris Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('CNN', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Andrew Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), (""Chris Cuomo's"", 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]","Chris Cuomo, the CNN anchor who is the brother of New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, has been diagnosed with the coronavirus, he announced Tuesday. Chris Cuomo's disclosure came as his brother briefed reporters on the increasing numbers of COVID-19 in New York state.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
95,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Hubei province', 'GPE'), ('67,801', 'CARDINAL')]","The new cases make New York the coronavirus epicenter of the world, surpassing China's Hubei province, which reported 67,801 cases.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
97,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Andrew Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('more than 67,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]","New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo is holding his daily press conference on the COVID-19 outbreak, which has infected more than 67,300 people in the state as of Wednesday.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
98,"[('Derek Scissors', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Hubei', 'GPE')]",Economist Derek Scissors said it is hard to believe China's COVID-19 outbreak did not spread more significantly outside Hubei province.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
99,"[('CNBC', 'ORG'), ('Jim Cramer', 'PERSON'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE')]","CNBC's Jim Cramer said Tuesday that a faster coronavirus test could turn the tide in fighting the outbreak — and by extension, the battered economy and the stock market.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
100,"[('Carnival', 'ORG')]","Carnival warned that ""even once travel advisories and restrictions are lifted, demand for cruises may remain weak for a significant length of time.""",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
101,"[('a ton', 'QUANTITY'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]","You're probably trying to stay in touch with friends, family and colleagues. There are a ton of video chat apps, and some are good for one purpose but not great for others. Here are some of the best video calling apps.",https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
102,"[('the Fire Department', 'ORG')]",The ambulances will increase capacity to transport coronavirus patients between medical facilities and assist the Fire Department with responding to a record number of medical calls.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
103,"[('4.9%', 'PERCENT'), ('2021', 'DATE')]",The firm still expects a rebound to 4.9% growth in 2021.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
104,"[('The U.S. Department of Transportation', 'ORG')]",The U.S. Department of Transportation will allow airlines to consolidate some of their service into a single airport to receive aid.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
105,"[('Belarussian', 'NORP'), ('Alexander Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('roughly 9.5 million', 'CARDINAL')]",Belarussian President Alexander Lukashenko has refused to implement a lockdown in the country of roughly 9.5 million people.,https://www.cnbc.com/id/10000108/device/rss/rss.html,CNBC
